John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Books, 1/1/1957-12/31/1989 (Box 705)
    A History of Soviet Russia: Von Rauch, Georg, 1957 [book]; A Century of Leadership: Founders Day Celebration, Newport News Shipbuilding, January 17-18, 1986 [booklet]; The Spirits of 76: Sloane, Eric, 1973 [book]; Code of Virginia, 1950, Title 11 - Rules of Virginia Supreme Court, 1984 Replacement Volume [book]; Foreign Relations and National Security Law: Franck, Thomas M. and Michael J. Glennon, 1987 [book]; US Army in World War II: European Theater of Operations - Cross-Channel Attack: Harrison, Gordon A., 1989 [book]; Code of Virginia, 1950, Title 8.01 - Civil Remedies and Procedure, 1984 Replacement Volume [book]; Committee on Armed Services, US Senate, 99th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, vols. I-III, 1986 [3 bound volumes]; Rules and Practices - Constitution: Jefferson's Manual, House of Representatives, 99th Congress, 1985 [bound volume]; Rules and Practices - Constitution: Jefferson's Manual, House of Representatives, 98th Congress, 1983 [bound volume]
  - Photographs, Floor Debate, and Audiocassettes, 11/14/1970-6/22/2006 (Box 706)
    Photo Album: USS Blue Ridge LCC-19 Commissioning, 11/14/1970 [spiralbound]; Reagan Speech, 9/27 [audiocassette]; Norfolk Debate, WHRO-TV, 9/26/1978 [audiocassette]; Fickett & Guest at 7th CD, 9/17 [audiocassette]; Debate - Richmond, 10/12 [audiocassette]; Surry News Conference - $61,000 [audiocassette]; Floor Debate on the Tower Nomination, 3/1989 [binder]; Friends of John Warner, 10/5/1995 thru 11/1/1996 [5 audiocassettes]; Loose Papers: Reprint of Congressional Record, 109th Congress, 2nd Session - "Senate Tribute to Senator John Warner, June 22, 2006"; Warner "Primary Radio", 5/9/1996 [2 audiocassettes]; Loose Portraits of Senator Warner; N. Virginia Chapter - Association of Govt. Accountants, 3/20/1984 [audiocassette]; Warner-Miller 2nd Debate [audiocassette]; Reagan PC & Reception [audiocassette]; GOP Meeting; Shad Planking; Women's Forum [VHH-C]; VNN "Commonwealth Conversation", 3/30/1996 [audiocassette]; Untitled Envelope: Reprint of Joint Resolution, 1/3/1980; Various Debates [audiocassette]; Virginia Federation of Republican Women [VHS-C]; Virginians for Warner Luncheon [audiocassette]; Warner Young Republicans, 3/23 [VHS-C]; Progressive Virginians Coalition [audiocassette]; Richmond Debate, 10/20/1978 [audiocassette]; Washington Post Luncheon, 8/6/1984 [audiocassette]; JWW and APM at Suffolk COC, 9/12/1978 [audiocassettes]; Photo Album: Launching of the SSN 753 Albany, 6/13/1987 [binder]; Debate - Vienna, 10/13 [audiocassette]; Untitled Audiocassette; JWW-APM - Bar Association [audiocassette]; Harrison/Warner Debate - League of Women Voters, 9/9/1984 [audiocassette]; "Ole no. 6" [envelope]; WGMS 570 AM, 103.5 FM - Guest Conductor Senator Warner, 12/23/1979 [audiocassette]
  - Daily Schedules (Anna Reilly), 10/1/2008-12/31/2008 (Box 707)
    10/1/2008-12/31/2008 (92 folders arranged chronologically)
  - VHS DVDs - Hearings, Interviews, Statements, 2/8/2000-9/25/2008 (Box 708)
    Fox News Interview w/Brit Hume, 11/7/2004 [VHS]; Nixon Center Ceremony Honoring, 2/8/2000 [VHS]; Senate Floor Statements from Senators Levin and Byrd, 6/22/2006 [CD]; PBS Newshour, 8/3/2006 [CD]; CNN Wolf Blitzer, 11/17/2005 [CD]; Press Conference on America's Climate Security Act, 8/2/2007 [CD]; US Senate Floor Statement, 2/17/2006 [CD]; Floor Coverage, 3/29/2001 [VHS]; Hardball, 2/12/2008 [CD]; JW/Rex NBC Story, 1/31 [VHS]; Armed Services Hearing, 9/23/2008 & 9/25/2008 [2 CDs]; Senator Warner - 10,000 Votes, 5/24/2006 [VHS]; NBC Meet the Press, 2/12/2006 [CD]; Press Conference - Iraq Resolution, 1/22/2007 [CD]; Levy Center Dedication, 9/18/2005 [CD]; Face the Nation; Meet the Press; Fox News Sunday; Late Edition, 10/30/2005 [CD]; Memorial - Naval Special Warfare, 7/8/2005 [DVD]
  - Memorabilia Items Listed By Item Number (Consult John W. Warner Memorabilia Inventory Database.mdb), [no dates given] (Box 709)
    WWO-0380; WWO-0752; WWO-0647; WWO-0646; WWO-0648; WWO-0338; WWO-0333; WWO-0337; WWO-0381; WWO-0332
  - Memorabilia Items Listed By Item Number (Consult John W. Warner Memorabilia Inventory Database.mdb), [no dates given] (Box 710)
    WWO-0401; WWO-0353; WWO-0750; WWO-0748; WWO-0751; WWO-0753; WWO-0747; WWO-0110; WWO-0628; WWO-0640; WWO-0745
  - Memorabilia Items Listed By Item Number (Consult John W. Warner Memorabilia Inventory Database.mdb), [no dates given] (Box 711)
    WWO-0678; WWO-0723; WWO-0677; WWO-0676; WWO-0708; WWO-0679
  - Memorabilia Items Listed By Item Number (Consult John W. Warner Memorabilia Inventory Database.mdb), [no dates given] (Box 712)
    WWO-0242; WWO-0339; WWO-0315; WWO-0644; WWO-0286; WWO-0113; WWO-0652; WWO-0378
- Senator John Warner papers (-bz), 1975-2009; MSS #10191_bz; 0.5 Cubic Feet 1 document box (Mss 10191-bz, Videocassette 0237, Disk 0895-001, Disk 0895-002, Oversizefolder MSS 10191-bz Oversize folder)
  Miscellaneous papers from the office of Senator John Warner consist chiefly of photographs and newsclippings. Photographs include Warner with Senator John McCain and President George W. Bush; with Mikhail Gorbachev and President Ronald Reagan; at St. Anselm's College receiving an honorary degree, 1975; at a Senate swearing in ceremony; the second inauguration of Bill Clinton including Al Gore, Jesse Jackson, Newt Gingrich, and Billy Graham; with Justices Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Anthony Kennedy, Sandra Day O'Connor, David Souter, Clarence Thomas; at the Chicago Board of Trade; with his 1984 office staff; and an official Senate portrait, 2007.
  Newspapers articles pertain to the Rappanannock River and the Woodrow Wilson Bridge over the Potomac.
  The collection also contains a selection of historical photographs and documents pertaining to Virginia copied from the holdings of the National Archives and Records Administration.
  The collection also contains a copy of a 2006 press conference on his trip to Iraq; a copy of his announcement not to seek reelection, 2007'.
  The collection also contains a disk of the Legislative Acitivity Report for his terms in office January 15, 1979 through January 2, 2009 and a videocassette of the 1997 inauguration of President Bill Clinton.
  Gift, Senator Warner, 225 Russell Senate Office Building, Washington, D.C. 20510, 202-224-2023, 2009 September.
  Iraq War, 2003-2011.; Professional papers.; Rappahannock River (Va.).; Woodrow Wilson Bridge.; Bush, George W, (George Walker), 1946-, Photographs.; Clinton, Bill, 1946-, Inauguration.; Clinton, Bill, 1946-, Photographs.; Clinton, Hillary Rodham, Photographs.; Gingrich, Newt, Photographs.; Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, Photographs.; Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich, 1931-, Photographs.; Gore, Al, 1948-, Photographs.; Gore, Tipper, 1948-, Photographs.; Graham, Billy, 1918-, Photographs.; Jackson, Jesse, 1941-, Photographs.; Kennedy, Anthony M., 1936-, Photographs.; McCain, John, 1936-, Photographs.; O'Connor, Sandra Day, 1930-, Photographs.; Reagan, Ronald, Photographs.; Saint Anselm College (Manchester, N.H.), Photographs.; Souter, David H., 1939-, Photographs.; Thomas, Clarence.; Warner, John W., 1927-, Photographs.
- Senator John W. Warner papers (-cb), 1978-2008; MSS #10191_cb; 2 compact discs (Disk 1146, Disk 1147)
  The discs contain Correspondence Archive General 1978-2008 and General Casework 1979-1995.
  Gift, United States Senate Historical Office, United States Senate, Washington, D.C. 20510, 2011 April 26.